boostmyshop.com 2017-02-27

# BoostMyShop.com Privacy Policy

                                        BoostMyShop.com
                                           Privacy Policy
BoostMyShop.corp (“Boostmyshop.com” or the “Site”) makes its extensions, services, and all
Site content available to you subject to this Privacy Policy and its Terms of Service. In this
Privacy Policy, "we", "us", "our" and other similar references mean Boost My Shop and "you"
and "your" and other similar references mean a specific user of the Site. If you visit the Site,
purchase an extension, request a service, or make an informational query, you accept the terms of
this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, or the Terms of Service, do not
use this Site, purchase extensions, or request services.
This Privacy Policy is in addition to your obligations and rights under the Terms of Service. For
the avoidance of doubt, in the event of a conflict between the Terms of Service and the Privacy
Policy or other terms and conditions posted on the Site, the Terms of Service will control. If you
are unsure of your rights under this Privacy Policy, please contact us at
contact@boostmyshop.com.
Your privacy is important to us. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so you understand (1)
what information we collect about our users, (2) how and why Boost My Shop collects it, (3)
how we protect it, and (4) the limited circumstances under which Boost My Shop may share it
with third parties.
GENERAL, ANONYMOUS NAVIGATIONAL INFORMATION:
General website navigational information collected through this Site may include the type of web
browser you use, the name of the domain from which you accessed the Internet, the Internet
address of the Site from which you linked to the Site, the pages and areas that you have visited
on this Site, the date and time you accessed this Site, and other non-personally identifiable
information. Website navigational information is collected to improve the content and
functionality of the Site and to customize the content or layout of this Site for specific users.
Cookies: Cookies are pieces of data assigned by a web server that uniquely identify the browser
on your PC, and enable our systems to gather information about your navigational patterns.
Boost My Shop attempts to install both persistent and session cookies when a user arrives at our
Site. Temporary "session" cookies ensure you are recognized when you move from page to page
on our Site, and that information entered is reused. We do not link the information we store in
cookies to any Personal Information you submit while on our Site. Persistent cookies, which stay
in one of your browser’s subfolders until deleted, allow us to remember your information and
settings for future Site visits.
Your web browser allows you to accept, disable, and delete cookies at any time; for more
information, see your browser’s “help” menu. Please note that if you block or refuse to accept
cookies, or delete cookies between visits to the Site, you may not be able to access or use certain
Site features or functions.

Our partners, affiliates, tracking partners and service providers may use session ID cookies to
make it easier for you to navigate our Site. We do not have access to or control over these
cookies.
Server Statistics: We, and our third party tracking partners, collect general, anonymous statistics
to track user trends on our Site, including hits to our server, the types of browsers used to access
our Site, page views, and navigational patterns. This information helps us track "where" our
users are coming from, pinpoint high traffic areas, and determine more effective communication
methods.
Log Files: We collect certain information automatically that is stored in our server’s log files,
such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your Internet service provider
(ISP), referring and exit pages, your operating system, and date/time stamp, automatically. We
use this information for Site administration, gathering client demographic information,
monitoring compliance with our Terms of Service, troubleshooting, and investigating security
breaches. We do not link this automatically collected data to your Personal Information
PERSONAL INFORMATION:
"Personal Information" is voluntarily provided information that identifies you, would enable
someone to contact you, or that describes your relationship with us, such as email address, name,
address or phone number. We collect and store Personal Information when you send us an e-
mail, register for a Boost My Shop account, purchase an extension, provide comments or submit
a problem, request information or support, or respond to Boost My Shop communications.
Below we inform you about the purposes for which we collect and use Personal Information, the
types of third parties to which Boost My Shop discloses Personal Information, and the choices
and means, if any, offered for limiting the use and disclosure of Personal Information.
Generally, we may maintain your Personal Information in order to satisfy your requests
and/or our business requirements. Personal information is used to fulfill your orders for our
extensions and services, respond to your inquiries, and provide requested information. We may
also use the information to inform you about new features, extensions, or services, and offer you
the possibility to unsubscribe this service While you are not required to submit any information
to our Site, if you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to access or use
some of the features and functions of our Site, and we may not be able to provide you with
certain services.
Duration: We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to
provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our
legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Access and Changes to Personal Information: If your Personal Information changes, or if you no
longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete, or deactivate it by making the change
on our your BoostMyShop.com account page or postal mail at the contact information listed
below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

 Collection Of Information From Children: Boost My Shop does not direct any of our content
 specifically to children nor do we knowingly collect personal information from individuals under
 the age of 13. If we learn that a user is under thirteen (13) years of age, we will promptly delete
 any Personal Information we have collected about that user.
 Consent To Processing In The United States: By registering on our Site and/or purchasing
 extensions and services through the Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the
 terms of this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of Personal Information across international
 borders in accordance with Boost My Shop's standard operations, including the collection,
 storage, if any, and processing of such information in other countries, and waive any rights that
 they may have under their local laws which would conflict with Boost My Shop's Privacy Policy.
 LIMITED CIRCUMSTANCES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION DISCLOSURE
 Boost My Shop takes reasonable measures to ensure that the confidentiality of its users’ Personal
 Information is maintained. We will share your Personal Information with third parties only to the
 extent and in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell your personal
 information to third parties.
 Parties Working for Boost My Shop: Boost My Shop uses certain trusted vendors and business
 partners to help us provide, improve, protect, and promote our services. These third parties will
 access your information only to perform tasks on our behalf and in compliance with this Privacy
 Policy. We ask all companies that act on our behalf to keep all information confidential and to
 use the Users information only to provide the services we ask them to perform for you and us.
 We may provide aggregate statistics about our users, sales, traffic patterns and related Site
 information to reputable third party vendors, but these statistics do not include Personal
 Information.
 Law and Order: We do not share your Personal Information except as specifically set forth in this
 Privacy Policy. We may share personal information with your consent or in good faith belief,
 subject to applicable laws, that is necessary:
 as required by law enforcement agencies or governmental bodies;
 to exercise or preserve our legal rights, such enforcing our Terms of Service, or the rights or
     property of other users;
 when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial
     loss or in connection with suspected or actual illegal activity;
 to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our Site or the public;
 as compelled by court order or other required legal process served on us, to the requesting
     party; or
 as otherwise authorized by you.
 External Links: We are not responsible for how non-affiliated companies or organizations
 collect, use, disclose, or secure the information that you provide to them. If you choose to access
 a third party website linked to our Site, you do so at your own risk and subject to any terms of
 service or privacy policy (if any) associated with such third party websites.

SECURITY
User privacy and security of Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally
accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during
transmission and once we receive it. We use physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards
to assist us in preventing unauthorized access, maintaining data accuracy, and correctly using
your Personal Information. We do not store sensitive information such as your credit card
number when processing your purchase orders. Any such information is processed directly
through third party partners, BEANSTREAM. No method of transmission over the Internet, or
method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its
absolute security.
When allowing Boostmyshop.com to set up modules or perform support on your own site,
opening a free access to your site, you do so at your own risk and you are solely responsible for
any associated damages to your computer or loss of data, at the present and as long as access is
open.
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83, a California resident who has provided
Personal Information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for
personal, family, or household purposes ("California Users") is entitled to request information
about whether the business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for the third
parties' direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of
Personal Information, upon receipt of a request by a California Users, the business is required to
provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed in the preceding
calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of Personal Information that were disclosed.
However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the
business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing
California Users' Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless
the California Users first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains
and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the
California Users of his or her right to prevent disclosure of Personal Information and providing a
cost free means to exercise that right.
As stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share information with third parties for their direct
marketing purposes. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications
from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later
decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the
third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should
always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how
that entity will handle your information.
California Users may request further information about our compliance with this law by
contacting us at contact@boostmyshop.com. Please note that we are only required to respond to
one request per user each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means
other than through our Site.

COMMUNICATIONS: When you register on our Site, we will use your email address to send you
e-mails about updates and special offers. If you wish to no longer receive these emails, please
follow the “unsubscribe” instructions contained in each e-mail. From time to time, out of
necessity, we will send you strictly service-related announcements. For instance, if our service is
temporarily suspended for emergency maintenance, we might send you an e-mail. Generally,
you may not opt-out of these non-promotional communications.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
Privacy Policy Changes: Boost My Shop reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy anytime
in its sole discretion. Your rights under this Privacy Policy will be subject to the most current
version of this Privacy Policy posted on this page at the time of your use. If we make any
material changes, prior to the change becoming effective, we will notify you by email (sent to the
e-mail address specified in your account) and/or by means of a prominent notice on this Site. We
encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy
practices.
Sale of Assets: If Boost My Shop is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion
of its assets, your information may be transferred as part of that deal. You will be notified via
email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal
information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
If you have questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices please
contact us via e-mail at contact@boostmyshop.com or via postal mail at 185 Alewife Brook
Parkway Suite 410,Cambridge MA 02138
